<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Solution</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable1_">Fable1_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_1_text">A sick Stag lay down in a quiet corner of his pasture-ground.
.
His companions came in great numbers to inquire after his health, and each one helped himself to a share of the food which had been placed for his use; so that he died, not from his sickness, but from the failure of the means of living.

 A sick Stag lay down in a quiet corner of his pasture-ground.
rsj9p,.His companions came in great numbers to inquire after his health, and each one helped himself to a share of the food which had been placed for his use; so that he died, not from his sickness, but from the failure of the means of living.

 </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable2_">Fable2_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_2_text">A young Man had been caught in a daring act of theft and had been condemned to be executed for it.

    He expressed his desire to see his Mother, and to speak with her before he was led to execution, and of course this was granted.

    When his Mother came to him he said: "I want to whisper to you," and when she brought her ear near him, he nearly bit it off. All the bystanders were horrified, and asked him what he could mean by such brutal and inhuman conduct.

    "It is to punish her," he said. "When I was young I began with stealing little things, and brought them home to Mother. Instead of rebuking and punishing me, she laughed and said: It will not be noticed. It is because of her that I am here to-day."

    "He is right, woman," said the Priest; "the Lord hath said: Train up a child in the way he should go; and when he is old he will not depart therefrom."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable3_">Fable3_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_3_text">A Dove shut up in a cage was boasting of the large number of the young ones which she had hatched.

A Crow, hearing her, said: "My good friend, cease from this unreasonable boasting. The larger the number of your family, the greater your cause of sorrow, in seeing them shut up in this prison-house."

 </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable4_">Fable4_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_4_text">The Hare was once boasting of his speed before the other animals.

"I have never yet been beaten," said he, "when I put forth my full speed. I challenge any one here to race with me."

The Tortoise said quietly, "I accept your challenge."

"That is a good joke," said the Hare; "I could dance round you all the way."

"Keep your boasting till you/ve beaten," answered the Tortoise. "Shall we race?"

So a course was fixed and a start was made.

The Hare darted almost out of sight at once, but soon stopped and, to show his contempt for the Tortoise, lay down to have a nap.

The Tortoise plodded on and plodded on, and when the Hare awoke from his nap, he saw the Tortoise just near the winning-post and could not run up in time to save the race.

Then said the Tortoise: "Plodding wins the race."</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable5_">Fable5_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_5_text">When first the Fox saw the Lion he was terribly frightened, and ran away and hid himself in the wood.

Next time however he came near the King of Beasts he stopped at a safe distance and watched him pass by.

The third time they came near one another the Fox went straight up to the Lion and passed the time of day with him, asking him how his family were,

and when he should have the pleasure of seeing him again; then turning his tail, he parted from the Lion without much ceremony.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable6_">Fable6_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_6_text">A Fox once saw a Crow fly off with a piece of cheese in its beak and settle on a branch of a tree.

"That's for me, as I am a Fox," said Master Reynard, and he walked up to the foot of the tree.

"Good-day, Mistress Crow," he cried. "How well you are looking to-day: how glossy your feathers; how bright your eye. I feel sure your voice must surpass that of other birds, just as your figure does; let me hear but one song from you that I may greet you as the Queen of Birds."

The Crow lifted up her head and began to caw her best, but the moment she opened her mouth the piece of cheese fell to the ground, only to be snapped up by Master Fox.

"That will do," said he. "That was all I wanted. In exchange for your cheese I will give you a piece of advice for the future. Do not trust flatterers"

 </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable7_">Fable8_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_7_text">At one time the Fox and the Stork were on visiting terms and seemed very good friends.

So the Fox invited the Stork to dinner, and for a joke put nothing before her but some soup in a very shallow dish.

This the Fox could easily lap up, but the Stork could only wet the end of her long bill in it, and left the meal as hungry as when she began.

"I am sorry," said the Fox, "the soup is not to your liking."

"Pray do not apologise," said the Stork. "I hope you will return this visit, and come and dine with me soon."

So a day was appointed when the Fox should visit the Stork; but when they were seated at table all that was for their dinner was contained in a very long-necked jar with a narrow mouth, in which the Fox could not insert his snout, so all he could manage to do was to lick the outside of the jar.

"I will not apologise for the dinner," said the Stork: "One bad turn deserves another."

 </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable8_">Fable7_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_8_text">Two Fellows were travelling together through a wood, when a Bear rushed out upon them.

One of the travellers happened to be in front, and he seized hold of the branch of a tree, and hid himself among the leaves.

The other, seeing no help for it, threw himself flat down upon the ground, with his face in the dust.

The Bear, coming up to him, put his muzzle close to his ear, and sniffed and sniffed.

But at last with a growl he shook his head and slouched off, for bears will not touch dead meat.

Then the fellow in the tree came down to his comrade, and, laughing, said

"What was it that Master Bruin whispered to you?"

"He told me," said the other: "Never trust a friend who deserts you at a pinch"

 </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable9_">Fable9_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_9_text">Once upon a time a Wolf was lapping at a spring on a hillside, when, looking up, what should he see but a Lamb just beginning to drink a little lower down.

"There's my supper," thought he, "if only I can find some excuse to seize it."

Then he called out to the Lamb, "How dare you muddle the water from which I am drinking?"

"Nay, master, nay," said Lambikin; "if the water be muddy up there, I cannot be the cause of it, for it runs down from you to me."

"Well, then," said the Wolf, "why did you call me bad names this time last year?"

"That cannot be," said the Lamb; "I am only six months old."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_fable10_">Fable10_Activity</string>
    <string name="fable_10_text">Once upon a time a Wolf was lapping at a spring on a hillside, when, looking up, what should he see but a Lamb just beginning to drink a little lower down.

"There's my supper," thought he, "if only I can find some excuse to seize it."

Then he called out to the Lamb, "How dare you muddle the water from which I am drinking?"

"Nay, master, nay," said Lambikin; "if the water be muddy up there, I cannot be the cause of it, for it runs down from you to me."

"Well, then," said the Wolf, "why did you call me bad names this time last year?"

"That cannot be," said the Lamb; "I am only six months old."
    </string>



</resources>
